迪 斯 尼 频 道 原 创 电 影
■
wqdsa倾情奉献
感谢破烂熊字幕组的字幕
一分钟人
■
翻译：公主   校对：稀饭cake
时间轴：草根没女 色妈妈麦麦
片源来自互联网，仅供学习、交流之用。
我发型怎么样?    很好 我的呢?
How's my hair?    Good. Mine?
很有型
Solid.
帅呆了!    帅呆了!
Scorch.
高中第一天 维吉尔
First day of high school, Virg.
终于进入美好的时光
We made the big time.
橄榄球 自习时间...女孩儿们
Football games, free periods... the chicks.
德里克? 你山洞里有蝙蝠    嗯?
Derek? You have a bat in the cave.    Huh?
鼻屎
Boogie fever.
只是试试你
And that was just a test.
难道这都成了紧急事件...
Had it been an actual emergency...
高中第一次打架
Their first high school fight!
我的男孩儿们长的真快
My boys are growing up so fast.
那时候的我们去哪儿了?
Where does the time go?
谁会在意过去? 伙计
Who cares about the past?
我在想未来的社交
l'm thinking about my social future.
我不想有什么改变
Well, l don't want anything to change.
此时此刻我已经有两个最好的朋友
l've got my two best guys right here, right now.
但我是你最爱的?
l'm your favorite though?
是吧 我完全够格
You can admit it. He's man enough to take it.
不敢相信你劝我
l still can't believe you talked me
去当啦啦队长
into trying out for cheerleading.
你会做的很好
You'll do fine.
我担心的是他
lt's him l'm worried about.
橄榄球的试训已经让他疯了
He's in full freak mode about football tryouts.
不用担心 我会去在精神上支持你
Don't worry, l'll be there for moral support.
你是说去打发时间?    没错
You mean to goof around?    Exactly.
这很严肃 你最好别让我难堪
This is serious. You better not embarrass me.
D石头 我从没要让你难堪
D-rock, l never try to embarrass you.
顺其自然而已
lt just works out that way.
但起先是一阵起哄
But first, a little boom-bah.
放松 保加
Relax, Beaugard.
人球合一 人球合一
Be the ball, be the ball.
那又怎样?
What's up with that?
待会见
l'll see you guys later.
好了 今天就这样
OK, that's enough for today.
不 等等 教练 我可以的
No! Wait! l can do this.
兄弟 先让你胳膊休息休息吧
Bro, maybe you ought to rest your arm.
什么声音?
What is that?
冲过来了!
Coming through! Whoa!
冲过来了! 它失控了!
Coming through! l can't control it!
真对不起! 小心!
l'm really sorry! Look out!
借过! 打扰了!
l'm sorry! Excuse me!
他毁了我的球场!
He's chewing up my field!
那个是不是你邻居?
lsn't that your neighbor?
是啊 查理·塔特尔
Charlie Tuttle.
我们班那个只有9岁的孩子
This kid in our class who's nine years old.
跳了很多级 是个天才
He skipped a bunch of grades because he's a genius.
是啊 还真是个爱因斯坦!
Oh, yeah. A real Einstein.
马上滚出我的球场!
Get off my field right now!
笨猪给我下来
Stupid dork's going down.
你要干什么?
What are you doing?
他马上就走了 不用管他
He's going away. Just ignore him.
这个真准!
Now that's some accuracy.
小东西
Little baby.
别这样! 让他休息会儿
Come on, give him a break.
别这样 嘿 德里克?
Hey, come on! Hey, Derek?
德里克 你也跳进来吧 很刺激
Derek, if you wanna jump in, that's cool.
德里克?
Derek?
放我下来! 放我下来!
Put me down! Put me down!
投的真棒! 不错 德里克!    好球!
Good throw! All right, Derek!    Nice shot!
谢谢你为我说话
Thanks for sticking up for me.
真的很抱歉会这样
l'm sorry about how it turned out.
请说我看起来不像你那么可笑
Please tell me l don't look as ridiculous as you do.
没那么糟糕 真的
lt's not that bad, really.
这个...这个红很配你
That's a... that's a nice red on you.
我是查理·塔特尔    维吉尔·福克斯
l'm Charlie Tuttle.    Virgil Fox.
很高兴见到你
Nice to meet you.
那个火箭车是怎么回事儿?
So, what's the story with that rocket cart thing?
公交车让我很不舒服 设想
l always get a hard time on the bus and l hypothesized
带火箭发动装置全地形车
a rocket-propulsion all-terrain cart
应能避免这种尴尬
would help avoid embarrassment.
你觉得怎么样?
Uh-huh. And how's that working out for you?
三 年 后
非常成功!
lt's working great!
我的情绪调制器让我完全理解了
My emotion modulator actually allows me to understand
艾伯特·菲林斯坦因
what Albert Felinestein
想通过他不同的"喵"声表达什么
is trying to communicate with his various meows!
是不是很振奋人心?
lsn't that amazing?
维吉尔? 看这里 维吉尔
Virgil? Hey! Earth to Virgil.
维吉尔! 你不这么想? 维吉尔
Virg! Don't you think, Virgil?
维吉尔? 你不感到兴奋吗?
Virgil? Aren't you excited?
当然 查理 你可以与猫交流了 我很激动
Yes, Charlie, l'm thrilled that you talk to your cat.
我不太确定
Um, l'm not entirely certain
我能肯定的是你在讽刺我
but l believe you may be employing sarcasm.
查理 你想要我怎么样?
Charlie, what do you want from me?
你的发明总能成功
Your inventions always work.
每次你说那些用果酸酱为房子提供能源
l can only act so surprised every time you figure out
的奇怪发明时 我只能表现出惊讶
how to power your house with tartar sauce.
这是鸡尾酱
lt's cocktail sauce.
你知道什么能让我开心吗?
You know what would make me happy?
要是你能发明些有用的东西
lf you built something useful.
有用 就是可以让我有钱
By useful, l mean something that would make me rich
或受欢迎 或者两者皆有
and popular. Or both.
你不能骑在这个上...
Hey, you can't ride that thing on the...
好车 真炫 铬合金 新型齿轮...
Hey, great bike. Lots of shiny, chrome, gear-y things.
你知道布丁里一些成分
Did you know that the contents of pudding
能让你长高吗?
actually makes you grow taller?
是这样啊    这就是为什么你这么高
lt does.    That's why you're so tall.
都是电解物之类的
lt's the electrolytes and everything.
拇指下去... 继续下去!
Thumbs down... and go!
好的! 我赢了!
Yes! l win!
都高三了 还是在这个笨蛋堆里吃饭
Senior year and l'm still eating at the dork table.
无意冒犯 伙计们
No offense, guys.
我非常享受这让人兴奋的谈话
l do enjoy the stimulating conversation.
没事儿
Hey, none taken.
老实说 怎么会这样?
But seriously, how did it come to this?
可能你的境况也许和
Let's see, maybe your plight has something to do with
头上戴着发饰
being stripped,
穿着迷你裙 挂在校吉祥物上有关
dressed in mini skirts, and hung from the school mascot.
一张上了年刊封面的照片
A picture made the cover of the yearbook.
还是连续三年
Three years in a row.
在所有的当地新闻报社
And on all the local news stations.
还有西语频道
And the Spanish Channel.
是啊 哪天我会请一个要价很贵的
Ah yes, the incident l will one day be explaining
治疗师解释解释这件事
to a very expensive therapist.
好呀 小蜂鸟
Hey, Hummingbird.
查理在和你问好呢
That's Charlie speak for ''hello.''
打扰一下 小姐
Um, excuse me, miss.
你为什么叫他"小蜂鸟"?
Why did you call him ''Hummingbird?''
我喜欢鸟 各种各样的鸟
Oh, l love birds. All kinds of birds.
大鸟 小鸟 我还是全美初级鸟友
Big birds, little birds. l'm even the official secretary
本地分会的秘书长
for the local chapter of the Junior Bird Buddies of America.
真是无上光荣
Such an honor!
好了 得走了
Anyway, gotta run.
不管怎样 整整发型
Fix that.
原来是这样
Well, that explains it.
珍妮特都追了你两年了?
Jeanette has been sweating you for two years.
你打算怎么办?
What's your deal?
别管它 我是科学的人
Forget it. l'm married to science.
祝贺你 兄弟
Hey, congratulations, buddy.
先走一步 先生们
Pardon me, gents.
苏打水
Ah, soda.
听说放一便士在里面一个星期后
l hear if you leave a penny in that stuff for a week
会亮不少
it comes out shiny?
我本来是想买瓶苏达
l was actually planning on drinking it.
不用担心
Well, never mind then.
你怎么样 维吉尔?
So, um, how are you, Virg?
这个暑假没见你几次
l didn't see you much this summer.
我经常去爬山
Oh, you know, l was doing a lot of mountain climbing
玩水上摩托什么的...
jet skiing...
打电动?    都没离开过沙发 你呢?
Video games?    l didn't leave the couch. You?
毫无新意乏味的聚会 啦啦队长营地
The usual, pool parties, cheerleading camp.
但参加了一个很不错建筑学班
But l did take this awesome architecture class.
真不赖
Oh, that's cool.
我记得你做过一个姜饼房
l remember you made a gingerbread house
有10个房间...
that had ten rooms...
还有可进入的壁橱
And walk-in closets.
我们吃了六个月
Took us six months to eat it.
得去上微积分了
Well, l have calculus.
讨厌它 需要它 想搞建筑离不开它
Hate it. Need it. Can't be an architect without it.
我是公共演讲
l got Public Speaking.
讨厌它 需要它
Hate it. Need it.
想当游戏节目主持 不得不学它
Can't be a game show host without it.
特斯拉的传记作者将他的书取名为
There's a good reason Tesla's biographer
《被埋没了的天才》有充足的理由
named his book A Man Out of Time.
他至今比同时代
Tesla was so far advanced over his contemporaries,
那些经常嘲笑他的
that they often derided...
那些经常嘲笑他是...
...they often derided him as...
小姐...
Miss...
乔斯林
Jocelyn,
要你在我的课上
is it too much to ask that you
别涂指甲是不是太过分了?
not do your nails while l lecture?
不好意思 您什么时候讲完?
Sorry. When are you done?
打扰了    塔特尔先生
Excuse me.    Ah, Mr. Tuttle.
是来拿你的加高椅的吧
l believe you're here for your booster chair.
我过会儿来拿 AV俱乐部紧急事件
l'll get it later. AV Club emergency.
我找维吉尔·福克斯有急事儿
l need Virgil Fox right away!
维吉尔·福克斯?    他生病了
Virgil Fox?    He's out sick.
可能不能去
l heard he might not make it.
真有趣 福克斯先生
Very funny, Mr. Fox.
你可以拿着离座证明离开
You can pick up your hall pass on your way out.
好吧 我这就去巴拉圭
That's it. l'm moving to Paraguay.
有看过我们的吉祥物吗?
Ever really looked at our mascot?
别管那个可笑的离座证明
Forget the hall pass.
记得带火箭发动装置
Remember that rocket-propulsion
全地形车的事儿吗?
all terrain cart the day of the incident?
谢谢你又说起来
Thanks for mentioning it again.
十分钟前刚有人提过
lt's been ten minutes since someone brought it up.
这两个有联系
Listen, it ties together.
那个可能不太成功
That invention may have not been a success,
但其中一个元素是用的
but one element of the design was proven viable.
量子加速器
The quantum accelerator.
记得我在物理学 新现实
Remember that physics, new reality
各方面理论的发明吗?
many worlds theory kick?
是啊 很有趣
Oh, yeah, that was fun.
我要在这些基础上建立自己的理论
l started building my own theory based on all of that work,
来一起证明我的量子加速器假想
incorporating my proven hypothesis of quantum acceleration.
我把学校的一台电脑设为永久贮存
l put one of the school's computers on permanent reserve.
数字用户回路已经开始工作了
The DSL has been doing all the work.
不久前
And moments ago
我刚解决了最后一个难题
l uploaded the last piece of the puzzle.
塔特尔长官 一切正常!
Commander Tuttle on the bridge!
伙计 别想要我跟你敬礼
Dude, no way l'm saluting you.
好吧 礼毕
Fine. At ease.
我要给你看的是非常
What l'm about to show you is very,
非常非常高度的机密
very, very top secret.
不准告诉第三个人
We have to keep this just between us.
看吧
Check it out.
怎么了?
Yeah?
你看到的
What you're looking at
是一个成功的虚拟现实时间隧道
is a successful simulation of practical time travel.
你干什么啊?
What are you doing?
让你脑子里的东西
l'm trying to stop any more of your brain
不要从耳朵里漏出去
from leaking out your ears.
什么?
What?
拜托 你昨天说我
Come on, yesterday you said
应该发明点有用的东西
l should build something useful.
时间隧道就是有用的
Well, time travel is useful.
查理 你已经14岁了
Charlie, you're 1 4 years old.
两年后就可以拿驾驶执照了
You're two years away from your driver's license,
却还是把内衣裤叫"小短裤"
you still call your underwear ''underpants''.
我可以相信你发明了一个时光机器吗?
l should believe you built a time machine?
当然 按照说明书
Yes! And based on my specifications
人们可以倒退
a person could travel up to 48 hours
48小时!    这太少了
into the past!    That's weak.
去你的 你时光机器能倒退多长时间?
Pardon me, how's your time travel formula coming along?
就像光一样 不是吗?
lt's all about light, right?
没有运动的更快的了
Nothing moves faster.
假设 你可以在
Well, my hypothesis suggests that
一束光中进行时光穿梭
you can time travel on a beam of light.
从任何光源
From any light source.
甚至是幻灯机的光
Even light from a slide projector.
幻灯机? 一个普通幻灯机?
A slide projector? Like a regular slide projector?
我说过普通吗? 没有 没说过
Did l say regular? No, l didn't.
我们说的是一个复杂的
What we're talking about is a complex amalgamation
电子零件合并还有内燃力机的机器
of electronic components and internal combustion mechanics.
顺便提一下 是你根本不了解的领域
Which you know nothing about, by the way.
得去找个搞机械的
We'll have to find a hardware guy.
这不是个问题
l don't see this as a problem.
小山雀! 在拌什么呢?
Hey, Chickadee! What's shakin'?
你得原谅查理
You have to excuse Charlie.
女孩让他很紧张
He's nervous around girls.
不 我没有    太帅了 我喜欢害羞的男生
No, l'm not!    Oh, it's cool, l like shy boys.
碗里的是什么?
Um, what's in the bowl?
蛋白酥皮小饼 作业
Meringue. The assignment.
拿我的吧 我再去做一个
Here, take mine. l'll make a new one.
看见了吗?    什么?
Did you see that?    What?
伙计 她把蛋白酥皮小饼给你了 太棒了
Dude, she gave you meringue. That's huge.
我只想知道
l just need to know
你到底帮不帮我?
are you going to help me with this or not?
你是要当一个参与者 铸就历史
Are you gonna be part of something, make history,
或者是局外的被动观察者
or sit on the sidelines and be a passive observer?
听着 约法三章
OK, look, l'll make you a deal.
我帮你找一个懂机械的
l'll help with your machine and find a hardware guy.
但第一次试验时
But when we try it out for the first time,
得用它做任何我想做的事
we use it for whatever l want to do.
行    好的
All right.    Right.
维吉尔 那个搞机械的一定要机灵
But Virgil, this hardware person we need is tricky.
为什么?
Why?
因为他不只需要有机械上的天赋
Because he not only needs to be gifted mechanically,
还要有一定道德柔韧性
but also, let's say, require a certain moral flexibility.
那些生活在社会边缘的人    好 那...
Lives on the fringes of society.    OK. Well...
他怎么样?    齐克? 你是说真的?
How about him?    Zeke? Are you serious?
看看他 他...他...
Look at him. He's, he's...
太完美了 在那些巨型卡车表演上
Perfect. You know, at those monster truck shows,
总有这个超级金属恐龙
there's always that giant metal dinosaur
吸着烟火 倒腾着汽车
that breathes fire and destroys cars?
我看过那个广告
l've seen the commercials
他和他爸爸在做这个东西
He and his dad build those.
杀手Saurus 颚破碎力量15,000磅
Killer-saurus. 1 5,000 pounds of jaw-crushing force!
了解!    小心 朋友们 这是食肉车!
l get it.    Look out folks, it's car-nivorous!
我知道了 知道了!
l get it! l get it.
你的猫吓到我了
Your cat is freaking me out.
不是我的猫 是他的
lt's not my cat. lt's his.
他叫艾伯特 菲林斯坦因
His name is Albert Felinestein.
这是我听过最蠢的猫名
That's the dumbest name for a cat l've ever heard.
非常赞成 齐克
Couldn't agree more, Zeke.
齐克斯特
Zekester.
我也讨厌别人把名字复杂化
l hate when people bend names too.
像"维吉尔奥斯特" 我会说
Like ''Virgilosity.'' l'm like,
"少来 伙计 叫维吉尔"
''Come on, people, it's Virgil.''
我这就不说了
l'm going to stop talking now.
艾米 不! 不! 不! 这是秘密会议
Amy, no! This is a private meeting.
不好意思
Oh, l'm sorry.
我下来看电视
l just came down to watch TV.
妈妈提过你有新朋友来
But Mom did mention you had a new friend over?
一个男生
A boy.
真恶心 天哪 维吉尔
Ew, he's gross! Geez, Virgil,
你就不能带个帅哥回家?
why can't you bring home cute boys?
艾米 走开
Amy, leave
不然我就告诉妈妈
or l tell mom you're doing makeovers
你又给仓鼠美容
on the hamsters again.
真失望 这就走
Chill. l'm outta here.
貌似我卷进了一场肮脏的竞赛
lt's like l walked into an ugly contest.
她还真可爱    是啊
She's a charmer.    OK.
这个东西 这个
OK, this thing, this, uh,
光计划物理特质的
quantum integration to the
量子加速器
physical properties of light projection,
好像能行得通
looks like it could work.
是的 芒戈语
Yeah, Mongo read.
好吧 你可以帮我们做吗?
OK. So you'll help us construct it?
为什么不?
Why not?
我喜欢挑战还有免费的豆条
l'm always up for a challenge. And free bean dip.
你有点...
Um, you have a little...
不要    ...有点豆末...
No.    ...some bean...
再这样 我就把你焊到城郊巴士上
Do that again and l weld you to the crosstown bus.
有想过我们要怎么用它吗?
Have you thought how we're going to use this thing?
第一次时光穿梭
The first journey back will
是一个里程碑
obviously be a monumental event
这次特别旅行的目标
and our specific goal on that journey
要适当的宏伟些
should be appropriately grandiose.
我知道了 两个字 先生们:
l got it. Two words, gentlemen:
彩票    太好了
The lottery.    Nice.
不行 维吉尔! 我拒绝同意
Absolutely not, Virgil! l refuse to agree to that.
但你早同意了
Oh, but you already did.
你说过只要帮你
You said that if l helped you,
我们可以用这个机器做我想做的任何事情
we'd use the machine for whatever l wanted to.
不准反悔!
No do-overs!
你到底想不想时间穿梭?
Do you want to time travel or don't you?
好吧    太棒了!
Fine.    Yes!
不会把这东西
You're not going to be able to just
就插墙上电源插座上吧
plug this thing into a wall outlet.
要很大的安倍数
This is gonna take major amperage.
还要有隐秘性和较大空间
Not to mention privacy and space.
我知道地方了 很棒的
l know the place. lt's perfect.
非常合适
lt's completely perfect.
拜托! 拜托!
Come on, come on!
托肯副校长
Vice Principal Tolkan,
我们需要谈谈开设新俱乐部的事
we need to talk about starting a new club.
不行
No can do.
我们已经没有教室可以用了
We're completely maxed-out on classroom space.
美国未来黄油社团是最后一个
The Future Fonduers of America were the last ones in.
在售货机里的是贾斯特吗?
ls that Chester in the vending machine?
伙计    谁有25美分?
Hey, fellas.    Does anyone have four quarters?
它不识别美元
lt's not taking my dollar.
你们想做些什么吗?
You going to do something?
什么? 改变高中的运行模式?
Like what? Change the way high school works?
不可能 先生们
No gentlemen.
世界的一切都有本身的法则
Everything in the world has an order.
有人被塞进了售货机
There are those who stuff others into vending machines,
有人从售货机买东西
and those who get stuffed into vending machines.
就是如此运作
lt's the way the system works.
这些在副校长手册里都有
lt's in the Vice Principal's handbook.
不管怎么样 我们的俱乐部
Anyway, about our club,
我们本想...    77号教室! 我们要77号教室!
we were wondering...    Room 77! We want room 77!
不可能 永远不会
lmpossible. Never gonna happen.
就像这个
Like this.
也许您可以再考虑考虑
Perhaps we can convince you to reconsider.
成交
Done.
好的 靠左一点
All right, scooch over to your left.
我要椒盐脆饼乾
l'm going after the Pretzel Nubs.
我们就在
The north wing was knocked down to make the football field,
北面的橄榄球场下面
which we're underneath now.
五十年代
Room 77 was built to be
77号教室是学校贮藏室
the school's fallout shelter back in the 1 950's.
我想穿过这儿就是
l think it's right through here.
有人称为教室改头换面(美国同名真人秀节目)
Someone call Extreme Classroom Makeover.
一团乱
This is a disaster.
不过确实是个好地方
Got great bones, though.
好的 完工
OK! This is it.
人类的一小步
One small step for man,
是巨大的...
but one very large...
不 不是的 一小步...
No, that's not it. lt's one small step for...
伙计 快启动啊
Dude, just turn it on.
好家伙!
Good gravy!
甩呆了!    是帅呆了
Scratch!    lt's scorch.
是的    谁想先去?
Right.    So who wants go first?
成为世界第一个时光穿梭者?
Be the world's first time traveler?
我刚吃了一个肉块三明治 会噎着的
l just ate a meatball sandwich. l might get cramps.
是啊 这是我最喜欢的新T恤
Yeah and um... this is my new favorite shirt.
拿上护目镜
Get the goggles.
好的 你太合适了    来吧 别咬
OK, you're good.    Come on, no biting.
好的    好了
OK.    OK.
艾伯特·菲林斯坦因在哪儿?
Where's Albert Felinestein?
你们...?
Did you...?
喂? 漩涡! 他会死的!
Hello? Vortex! He could die!
我进去你就满意了 什么...
You were OK with me going in there. What...
但我正要...    抓住了!
But l was gonna...    Hang on!
哇 穿梭猫
Whoa, a catsicle!
维吉尔 时光穿梭时
Virgil, time travel is unpredictable.
温度有很大的变数!
The temperatures can be highly variable!
兄弟们? 看看表
Guys? Take a look at the watch.
8:43
8:43.
8:44
8:44.
整整差一分钟 这就是说...
An exact one-minute differential. That means...
你的猫是历史上第一个时光穿梭者!
Your cat is the first time-traveler in history!
我们成功了!
We did it!
太奇怪了
Huh. That's bizarre.
萨莫顿高中有情况
l've got a reading from the Summerton sensor
出现很多图表
pretty much off the charts,
但周围什么也没有
but nothing around it. Hmm.
他们楼里有什么东西?
You think they got anything on that upstairs?
不能 有问题他们肯定会打电话的
Nah, they would've called right away.
可能是一些电脑小故障
Probably another computer glitch.
他们给我们这些住地下室的提供很傻逼的器械
They give us basement dwellers the lame-o equipment.
加上满楼好吃的零食
Plus all the good snacks are upstairs.
我很严肃 尝尝这个 好像坏了
l mean, seriously, try one of these, they're stale.
斯蒂芬 我要怎样你才能相信?
Steph, what do l have to do to make you believe me?
她只是教我法语
She's just teaching me French.
乔斯林·李 给你当法语家教
Hmm, Jocelyn Lee is tutoring you in French
就这样?
and that's all?
瞧 这就是为什么需要她的帮助
See, that's why l need her help.
我根本不懂你说什么
I have no idea what you said.
我说"我的男朋友是个说谎的弱智"
l said, ''My boyfriend is a lying cheesebrain.''
别这样 斯蒂芬
Come on, Steph,
乔斯林很性感 但却是个低等的进食者
Jocelyn's hot but she's a total bottom feeder.
我不会再过去了
l would never go there.
知道了    待会打电话给你 行了?
l know.    l'll call you later, OK?
好的
OK.
没看见你在这儿    你好
Oh, Steph, l didn't see you there.    Oh, hey.
在学习?
You studying?
我在找卷笔刀
l was looking for a pencil sharpener.
我这儿有
Oh, l have one.
你有铅笔吗?
Do you have a pencil?
老样子 维吉尔 一点没变
Same old Virg. Never changes.
你也没怎么变
Well, you haven't changed much either.
跑过浇水管
Does your hair still frizz up
你头发还会是一团乱?
when you run through the sprinkler?
当然 早上来学校前
Totally. This morning before school
我还在草坪上装了个胶水管
l set up the Wiggly Worm on the lawn...
我喜欢胶水管
l love the Wiggly Worm.
还记得那次我差点淹死了吗?
Remember that time l almost drowned?
因为德里克把喷头对着你鼻子
Because Derek shoved the nozzle up your nose.
他拼命的跑
He tried to run away
头还撞了电话线杆
and cracked his head on the telephone pole.
真想那时的我们    三个好朋友
l miss us.    Tres amigos.
是啊
Yeah.
你知道吗
You know
德里克尽力去阻止那些橄榄球员了
Derek really did try to stop those football players.
但他们是高年级的
But you know how seniors are.
无论如何
Anyway
他对那天的事很难过
l know he feels bad about what happened that day.
他们说
You know, they say that
放不下过去的人死的更快
people who don't let go of the past die faster.
会有更多的痛苦
And get more acne.
我汗流浃背了
l'm sweating like five hogs.
因为气温的变化不定
Due to irregularities in temperature
我们应该准备好
we should be prepared.
我们就在这儿买彩票吧
OK, l got the winning lottery numbers right here.
为了保证我们回来时
To guarantee that the vortex maintains
漩涡能保持平稳
stability long enough to return safely,
我们只有10分钟的时间
we only have ten minutes on the other side.
否则 会引发爆炸
Otherwise, we run the risk of exploding.
有趣 还以为你说的是爆炸
That's funny, l thought you said exploding.
是说了 放射性网络
l did. Activating grid...
带着钩子干什么?
Um... what's with the grappling hook?
你嘲笑这钩子?
You making fun of the hook?
什么? 不 不是 喜欢 喜欢这钩子
What? No, no. Love, love the hook.
下一站...新式小镇
Next stop... funky town.
想起来 我忘了 检查三次...
l just remembered. l forgot to triple check the...
我们可以商量商量这个吗?
Can we talk about this?
要改进我们着陆的地方
We gotta work on our landings.
昨天1 :27 我们成功了
1 :27 yesterday. We did it.
是啊 成功了 我们是时光穿梭者
Oh yes, we did it. We're time travelers.
我们是时光穿梭者 我们是时光穿梭者
We're time travelers We're time travelers
我们是时光 我们是时光
We're time, we're time,
我们是时光 我们是时光 我们是时光穿梭者
we're time we're time, we're time travelers
我们是时光穿梭者    他还正常吧?
We're time travelers    ls he OK?
他真的很热爱科学
He really loves science.
我们是时光穿梭者 我们是时光穿梭者
We're time travelers We're time travelers
买一张彩票 这是数字
One lottery ticket, please. These are the numbers.
我们感到很幸运
We're feeling lucky.
你觉得你有身份证吗?
Are you feeling like you have l.D.?
买彩票必须要满18岁
You need to be 1 8 to buy a lottery ticket.
我们需要你帮个忙
Hi. We need to ask you a favor.
他想要小费
He wants a tip.
放这了
Here, OK.
想要你替我们买张彩票
We need you to buy us a lottery ticket
这是号码
with these numbers.
你觉得怎么样?
What do you say?
给小费
Tip him.
我就这些了 行吗?
lt's all l got, OK?
伙计们 伙计们
You guys. You guys!
我们还有两分钟时间回学校
We have two minutes to get back to school!
新方案 明天12点这儿见
New plan. We'll meet you here tomorrow at 1 2:00.
到时要拿好彩票 行吗?
Hang on to the ticket till then, OK?
好的
OK.
第二次波动
OK, that's the second fluctuation
同一大小
of the same exact magnitude,
同一地点
at the same exact location.
告诉你了 是技术故障而已
l'm telling you, it's a technical glitch.
还有可能是什么?
What else could it be?
你觉得他们突然
You think they all of a sudden started
在萨莫顿挖油?
drilling for oil in Summerton?
回去做自己的事儿吧
Now, let's just get back to work, all right?
能帮我把这个解开吗?
Can you help me un-knot this?
太帅了 不敢相信他赢了
Cool. l can't believe he won.
今天下午一个令人难以置信的故事
An incredible story from Summerton this afternoon.
昨晚公布州立彩票的赢家
The winner of the State Lottery, announced last night,
就是这个机器人
has turned out to be none other than Robot Man.
告诉过你了
Told you.
好吧 明天我们再回来
OK, so tomorrow we go back in time
买一张新的
and get a new lottery ticket.
不过这次我们得保证...    不行
But this time, we be sure...    No.
维吉尔 这是不对的
Virgil, it's wrong.
这是作弊
lt's cheating.
你说的对 就是作弊
You're right. lt is cheating.
新方案
New plan.
我们在电视上给它打广告 做电视导购
We go on TV with the machine, do an infomercial,
卖8000台 我们就会有源源不断的财富
sell like 8,000 of them and instantly become rich
受大众追捧
and humongously popular!
他们说你不能买到幸福
And they say you can't buy happiness.
听着
Listen to me.
要是有其他人发现了这个时光机
lf anyone finds out about this time machine
那时就是我 你 还有齐克的末日
it will be the end of me, you, and Zeke.
末日!
The end!
你能转过身去吗? 我不喜欢和人近距离接触
Can you back up? l have personal space issues.
不
Oh, no.
思维不要被局限了
Think outside the box.
这个机器有很大的用处
There's an important use for the machine.
有什么比财富和名气还重要?
What's more important than being rich and popular?
开玩笑! 我在开玩笑 本来就是
Kidding! l'm kidding... mostly.
贾斯特 在找这个啊
Hey, Chester. Looking for these?
把衣服还我
Hey, gimme those!
禁止嚼口香糖
要是你想试试新形象
lf you're trying out a new look
老实说 不怎么样
let me say it's not working.
那些人偷了我衣服
Those kids stole my clothes.
能帮我拿回来吗?
Can you help me get them back?
很乐意 真的 我会的
l'd like to. Really, l would.
但这意味着
But that would mean altering
改变学校规范制度
the delicate social system at the school.
祝你好运
So... good luck.
维吉尔 我有个好主意
Virgil, l just had a brilliant idea.
你是说用时光机...    没错
You mean use the time machine to...    Exactly.
呆瓜!    再来一次 是帅呆了
Starch!    Again, scorch.
你有读过我邮给你的指导书吗?
Did you read the instructions l e-mailed you?
对不起
l'm sorry.
好的 直接点
OK, so let me get this straight.
你是说我们做无名英雄?
You're saying we become like silent heroes
一点都不酷?    看看周围
to the un-cool?    Look around.
我们可以用几分钟
We live in a world where mere minutes
改变整个未来
can make or break a person's entire future.
想想 高一发生了什么?
Take what happened freshman year.
它毁了我的生活
Had l known it would ruin my life,
我本不该这样做
l never would've done it.
这是你真实想法吗?
Tell us how you really feel?
想想学校里所有
Think about all the kids at this school
像贾斯特 像我们的孩子
like Chester, like us.
我们生活在长期的恐惧羞辱中
We all live in constant fear of humiliation,
因为我们偶然的成为弱小
because we happen to be smaller
不融洽之类的
less coordinated, whatever.
但我们可以改变
But we can change that.
一分钟人要用他们的力量
The Minutemen must use their powers
来维护真理与正义
for truth and justice.
接下来我们就可以集中注意力赚钱了
And then we focus on getting rich.
我在开玩笑
Again, l'm kidding.
谁是一分钟人?    我们 我们就是
And who are the Minutemen?    We. Us.
及时的出现在重要的时刻
The all-important minutes in time.
很聪明 对吧?    确实
Clever, right?    Sort of.
不觉得
Not really.
别管这个
Forget it!
这些遥控器没一个好用
None of these remote control hookups are gonna work.
这个一点也不好
This is no good.
要调整调整 我们得准时回来
We have to make adjustments while we're back in time.
那 我们其中一个得留下来
Well, then, l guess one of us is going to hang back.
不要!    不要
Not it!    Not it.
不要! 去你的!
Not it! Aww! Dang it!
这不公平 我发明了这个机器    好吧
Unfair, l invented the machine.    OK.
再来一次 不要!    不要!
Re-do. Not it!    Not it!
不要! 去你的!
Not it! Double dang it!
不要! 这个真有趣
Not it! That was fun.
不要!    珍妮特你来这儿干什么?
Not it!    Uh, Jeanette, what are you doing here?
我想参加一个俱乐部 我看见你们的了
l was looking for a club to join and l saw yours.
"回到过去俱乐部"      是啊
''The Back To The Future Fan Club.''    Oh, right.
我喜欢这电影 虽然我没看过
l love that movie, even though l never really saw it.
但我很喜欢时间穿梭这主意
But l totally love the idea of time travel.
这个非常...科幻
l mean, it's just so... science fiction-y.
珍妮特 来的正巧
Actually Jeanette, your timing is interesting.
不 不行 维吉尔 你想怎么样?
No, it isn't, Virgil. What are you doing?
抱歉
Uh... Excuse us.
会一团乱的...
Shh!    lt's gonna mess up...
不行 不行 不行!    听我说
No, no, no!    Listen to me.
不行 不行 不行    想想会发生什么
No, no, no.    Think about what's going on.
好了
OK.
珍妮特请坐
Jeanette, have a seat.
是的 善知鸟
Sure thing, Puffin.
但先...
Um... but first...
我们得换套装束
We so have to do something about those outfits.
去吧 好了不少
There you go. That's better.
你从哪儿弄的啊?
Where did you get these?
我爸爸在滑冰世界买的
My Dad just bought Ski World.
很幸运?
How lucky is that?
要是他还有一个虾仁华夫小屋
lf he still owned The Shrimp 'n Waffle Hut
那真是棒的不可救药
that would be like, no help at all.
我正在找要穿什么呢
l've been looking for something form-fitting
能够聚焦这些大型的枪支
that would highlight these massive guns.
你看上去像个吉娃娃
You're built like a chihuahua.
你看起来像个雪人
You look like a yeti.
你以为我不知道雪人是什么样?
You think l don't know what a yeti is?
你知道吗?
Do you?
维吉尔快长大吧
Virgil, grow up.
我 长大? 你才要长大!
Me, grow up? You grow up!
不要吼查理!
Don't yell at Charlie!
我没有!你不要吼
l'm not! You stop yelling!
我从来不对其他人大喊大叫
l never yell at people.
不要吵了!
Stop yelling!
没想过时光穿梭会这么吵
l never thought time travel would involve so much bickering.
哦 天哪
Oh, man!
站着别动 伙计
Hold it right there, friend.
要是想戏弄我
Uh, if you guys are gonna pick on me
你们得拿号码牌了
you'll have to take a number.
不要害怕    我们来帮助你
Don't be afraid.    We're here to help.
怎么了 伙计?
What's going on, fellas?
那个你拿着吧 我有新衣服了
Oh, you can keep those. l got myself some new threads.
穿雪衣的小子是谁啊?
Who were those snowsuit guys?
经过二十年的服务
After twenty years of service
董事会会给你金表或者其中任何一个
the board gives you either a gold watch or one of these.
我可爱的小城堡
My sweet little castle.
不要碰
Don't touch it.
等装好防弹玻璃罩后要放进我办公室的
lt's going in my office in a bulletproof glass case.
它很柔弱
lt's delicate.
我们赢了吗? 我们赢了吗?
Did we win? Did we win?
我们赢了 非常成功
Oh, we won all right. We won big.
瑞切特护士 鲍勃教练
Nurse Ratchett and Coach Bob
曾见过 他们确认这不会传染
have seen it before and they assure me it's not contagious.
在我们结束今天早上的广播前 还有一件事
One more thing, before we wrap up this morning's announcements.
最近有一群学生穿着雪衣
Recently, a group of students dressed in snowsuits,
干扰体育课
disrupted a gym class.
更重要的是 毁坏了我珍惜的透视模型
More importantly, they destroyed my precious diorama.
不管是谁 我明确声明
Whoever you students are, let me make it perfectly clear
一旦查出你们的身份 会受到严肃处理
that once you are identified, you will be severely punished.
就到这里
That is all.
太酷了 我们成了绿林好汉
Cool. We're outlaws.
警察在追捕我们    淘气的内德
On the run from Johnny Law.    Naughty Neds.
我忘用牙线洁牙 妈妈就会这么说我
That's what my mom calls me when l forget to floss.
很好 不过我觉得这是垂悬分词
Perfect, except l think that's a dangling participle.
我讨厌这些东西垂悬
l hate it when those things dangle.
等五分钟 行吗?
Pick up in five minutes, OK?
我真的很累 我想坐下来歇歇
l'm totally tired and need to sit down.
你可以拿点吃的来吗?
You think maybe you could just bring the food to our table?
你懂的 违反点纪律
You know, bend the rules just a little bit?
尤金·梵·霍则伯格
Eugene von Hoserberg.
好吧    太棒了
Uh... You bet.    Great.
懂了吗?
So, do you think you get it?
是的
Um... yeah.
这就来...
Here you go...
真不错 笨猪
Nice one, dork.
中彩了 尤金
Way to go, Eugene.
尤金·梵·霍则伯格
Eugene von Hoserberg.
好吧    太棒了
Uh... You bet.    Great.
来吧    好样的! 雪衣小子!
Here you go.    All right! The Snowsuit Guys!
好样的! 雪衣小子!
All right, the Snowsuit guys.
太棒了 雪衣小子!
Way to go, Snow Guys.
恭喜啊 尤金
Way to go, Eugene.
到此为止 滑雪俱乐部! 或者我该说
The jig is up, Ski Club! Or should l say...
雪衣小子?
...Snowsuit Guys?
是啊 我总是跟他们一起聚会
Yeah, l party with them all the time.
你们说的是谁? 尤金
Who's this we're talking about, Eugene?
维吉尔 不是别人
Oh, hey, Virgil. Yeah, it's nobody you know.
我在说雪衣小子
l'm just talking about the Snowsuit Guys.
是啊 我听说过他们
Oh, yeah, l heard about them.
他们简直是真正的英雄
They're supposed to be total heroes.
我听说那个中等身材的小伙子非常幽默
Oh, and l hear the medium height guy, is extremely hilarious
相当英俊...
and devastatingly handsome...
他们叫一分钟人 不是雪衣小子
And they're called the Minutemen, not the Snowsuit Guys!
有人注意尤金的态度吗?
Anyone notice that Eugene has copped an attitude?
态度? 看看贾斯特吧
You want attitude, check out Chester.
是我引领的潮流吗? 你告诉我吧 伙计
Am l a trend setter? You tell me, amigo.
这些小子
l mean, who else are these kids
都跟着谁的风格?
supposed to look up to to set trends?
那人蠢人?
Those doorknobs?
维吉尔? 维吉尔 维吉尔!
Virgil? Virgil, Virgil!
我本想昨晚给你打电话 但还是亲自告诉你吧
l almost called you, but l wanted to tell you in person.
什么? 怎么了?    贝尔蒙大学录取我了!
What? What's going on?    l got accepted into UC Belmont!
太棒了!
Get out!
但还不完全如此
But it's not a done deal yet.
我在申请啦啦队长奖学金
l applied for a cheerleading scholarship.
他们派来一个调查员
They're sending a scout,
我得努力做好我的金字塔下马
which means l have to work on my pyramid dismount.
太酷了 我为你高兴 你喜欢那个学校
That's so cool! l'm so psyched for you! You love that school!
斯蒂芬!    德里克
Steph!    Oh, Derek.
我得去告诉他奖学金的事儿
Oh.    Gotta tell him about the scholarship.
待会儿见 维吉尔 拜拜
So, l'll see you later, Virg. Bye.
查理 怎么了?
Charlie, what's wrong?
关于时光机
OK, there's something l haven't told you
我有些没有告诉你们
about the time travel formula.
记得有一个困扰我几年的
Remember there was one last piece of
最后一个方程式
the equation that evaded me for years
直到我日以继夜的
until l found what l was looking for
通过因特网下载程序才解开
through a round-the-clock internet downloading procedure.
他非法进入数据库?    还要糟糕
He was hacking.    lt gets worse.
我从NASA偷的    你抢了NASA?
l stole it from NASA.    You robbed NASA?
没有听上去那么糟糕
lt's not as bad as it sounds.
不 比听上去的还要糟糕
Yes, it's worse than it sounds.
那些是六十年代的 他们已经无效了
The files were from the 1 960s, they were defunct.
几十年没人碰过了
No one has touched them for decades.
这很糟 非常糟
This is bad, real bad.
我们可能会进监狱    你知道
We could go to prison.    Just so you know,
要是我们坐牢了 得用一个牢房
if we do go to prison, and we share the same cell,
我鼾声就像拉锯一样
l snore like a chain saw.
很好    这不是问题
Great.    This won't be a problem
只要我们一段时间不用这个机器 潜伏起来
as long as we don't use the machine for awhile and lay low.
弄掉了一颗葡萄
Mmm, l dropped a grape.
怎么会这样?
So, how did it happen?
别想了 斯蒂芬妮
Forget it. lt's terrible Stephanie
从金字塔上摔下来确实很糟糕
fell off the top of the pyramid.
但别想了
But forget it.
我们都被监视了 对吧
l mean, we all said that we were being watched, right?
都火烧眉毛了
The heat is on.
要是我们不帮斯蒂芬妮 她会失去奖学金的
lf we don't help Stephanie she could lose out on her scholarship.
我们得回去    因为你暗恋她!
We have to go back.    'Cause you have a creepy crush on her!
暗恋? 我也这么认为
Oh! Creepy crush. l vote yes!
查理 说说你自己
Charlie, you said it yourself
非法搞到的过期文件
the files you hacked into were defunct.
我保证没有人知道他们失踪了
l'll bet nobody knows they're missing.
需要我再提醒你一次吗?
Need l remind you?
我们是一分钟人 不是 胆小人
We are the Minutemen, not the Weeniemen.
晚饭前回来哦!
Don't be late for dinner!
我们得计划一下
OK, we need a plan of action.
我们必须非常小心
We've got to be extremely discreet.
勇敢和果断
And bold and decisive.
齐克 你怎么想?    他去哪儿了?
Zeke, what do you think?    Where'd he go?
齐克?    他去哪儿了?
Zeke?    Where'd he go?
至少我们有了勇敢和果断
At least we got the bold and decisive part.
冲啊 冲啊 冲啊!
Go, go, go!
回来! 快
Come back here! Come on.
雪衣小子
Snowsuit Guys.
怎么了 尤金    伙计 我能一块来玩儿吗?
What's up, Gene.    Hey, dudes. Mind if l hack in?
站住 不准动!
Stop! Hold it right there!
加油 公羊!
Go Rams! Whoo!
接的真准!
Good catch!
我不知道你是谁 但真让人惊讶
l don't know who you are, but you're amazing.
少来
Get out.
雪衣小子 雪衣小子!
Snowsuit Guys, Snowsuit Guys!
少来...
Get... whoa!
真棒!    雪衣小子!
All right!    Yeah! Snowsuit Guys!
我们叫一分钟人!
And we're called the Minutemen!
根据我的计算 你们都跟我的风
According to my calculations, you guys are in my way.
少管我们 贾斯特    我不喜欢你的帽子
Leave us alone, Chester.    l'm not fond of your hat.
打扰了 这里怎么了?
Excuse me, what is going on here?
贾斯特总骚扰我们
Chester keeps harassing us.
闭嘴 混蛋    都静一下
Shut up, dirtball.    Everyone, settle down.
贾斯特我记得
Chester, last l remember
你是食物链的最底层
you were at the bottom of the food chain
我不能忍受学生
and l will not tolerate students
蛙跳到高等阶层
leapfrogging to a higher social status.
跟我来
So you come with me.
要公羊角报吗?    谢谢
The Ram's Horn?    Thanks.
不客气    我要一份?
Sure.    can l have one?
"机器人控告老太太" 维吉尔 这很糟糕
''Robot Man Sues Old Lady''?    Virgil, this is bad.
我们改变了没有料到的事物发展的后果
We are changing the outcome of things we never planned on.
我们的改变造成了连续反应    那又怎么样?
Our jumps cause a chain reaction.    How so?
贾斯特陷入困境 这在之前是不可能发生的
Chester getting in trouble. That's never happened before.
机器人控告老太太? 世界都疯了
Robot men suing old ladies?  lt's a world gone mad!
就像我说的一样 疯了
Mad l tell you!
全球变暖 让他很抓狂
Global warming. He's really freaked out.
需要帮忙吗?
Hey, you, uh, need a hand?
斯蒂芬
Uh... Steph.
不 不用了
Um, not, not really.
你来有...?    只是看看我能做什么
What are you...?    l figure it's the least l can do,
来感谢你    为什么?
to thank you.    For what?
你救了我 雪衣小子
For saving me. Snowsuit Guy.
什么? 不是 不是 不是      不要这样 维吉尔
What? Oh, no, no, no.    Oh, don't even try it, Virg.
"少来" 拜托
''Get out?'' Please.
你 查理 齐克·汤普森
You, Charlie, and Zeke Thompson
就是雪衣小子    斯蒂芬...
are the Snowsuit Guys.    Steph...
我知道 这太帅了
l knew it! That is so cool!
我想想就发现了
l figured it out because l started thinking.
你们会在坏事发生之前
The kids you helped
帮助那些孩子
it was before something bad was about to happen,
比如我那件事儿    太可笑了
like with me.    That is ridiculous.
我们怎么能知道坏事什么时候会发生?
How are we gonna know when something bad is gonna happen?
这就是我问自己的
That's exactly what l asked myself.
我想了又想
l thought about it and l thought about it.
然后就知道了    不 你不知道
Then l figured it out.    No, you didn't.
是的 我知道了    不
Yes, l did.    No.
不可能知道    承认吧 维吉尔
You couldn't have.    Admit it, Virgil.
你 查理 还有 齐克...
You, Charlie and Zeke...
是巫师    时光穿梭者?
...are psychic.    Time travelers?
什么? 有人说"时光穿梭者"吗?
What? Who said ''time travelers''?
不 这太疯狂了 不可能      少来!
No, that's crazy. We're psychic.    Get out!
我们是巫师 我听你说的...是的 不会吧 不会吧 不
We're psychic. l heard you...    No, no, no.
维吉尔 你说时光穿梭者
Virgil, you said time travel.
喔 上帝 酷毙了 你怎么弄的?
Oh my gosh, cool! How do you do it? Huh? Huh?
准备!
Down!
暂停!
Time out!
这场城郊比赛还剩7秒
Six seconds left in this match of crosstown rivals.
黄蜂在第四节
The Hornets cling to a four-point lead
领先萨莫顿四分
coming on fourth and goal for Summerton.
橄榄球 再说一遍为什么我们在这里
Football. Remind me why we're here again.
因为一些人总会在这时候让自己丢脸
'Cause some kid always embarrasses himself at these things.
睁着眼睛看就行
Just keep your eyes open.
我真的很聪明
You know, l'm actually very bright.
还有很多人都觉得我是蓬勃异常
Even though a lot of people see me as sputty.
蓬勃异常?    就是生气蓬勃而且头脑异常
Sputty?    A cross between spunky and nutty.
很好
Great.
听着 保 一切都在你手中 但不要有压力
Listen, Beau, it's all in your hands, but no pressure.
行吗? 别想还剩六秒钟
All right? Forget that there's six seconds left on the clock.
别想你可能让萨莫顿高中出现在地图上
Forget that you could put Summerton High on the map.
别想我的小儿子在人群里
Forget my little boy is up there in the stands,
看着他的爸爸努力实现毕生的梦想
looking down on his father trying to fulfill a lifelong dream
获得全州冠军 什么都别想
of winning a state championship. Forget about all that.
我只想要你...
What l want is you...
...要你...
...you, to, uh...
人球合一?    人球合一
Be the ball?    Be the ball.
人球合一! 把他们一举拿下!
Be the ball! Go get 'em!
准备! 蓝队 二十二!
Down! Blue, twenty-two!
冲啊 公羊 冲啊!    蓝队 二十二!
Go Rams go!    Blue, twenty-two!
准备! 进攻!
Set! Hike!    Whoo!
结束了 托肯! 完结了 托肯!
Down with Tolkan! Done with Tolkan!
结束了 托肯!
Down with Tolkan!
裸奔男孩儿 他满场跑
For a guy with nudity issues, he's come full circle.
失球! 比赛漏球!
Loses the ball! There's a fumble on the play!
哈密尔顿拿到球!
And Hamilton's got it!
大黄蜂赢了!伤心的萨莫顿!
The Hornets win! What a heartbreaker for Summerton.
我早知道你会有大成就的 维吉尔
l always knew you were gonna do big things, Virg
时光穿梭对吧?
but time travel?
真是难以置信 兄弟
That's whacked out, man.
一 二 三 四 你的球队臭名扬永远不得分
One, two, three, four Your team stinks. You'll never score!
艾米...    五 六 七 八
Amy...    Five six seven eight
你不可能追上 我很棒
You can't touch this. l'm too great.
艾米够了 上楼
Amy, that's it. Upstairs!
斯蒂芬妮 我都没看到过你 你来真是太奇怪了
Stephanie, l didn't even see you. lt's so weird that you're here.
天哪 德里克·保加?
And oh my gosh, Derek Beaugard?
你是最棒的橄榄球运动员...
You are like the best football player ever...
...除了昨天的失算的比赛
...except for that blown play yesterday.
快走 艾米看动画片去    不要
Just go. Amy, go watch cartoons.    No.
真的很不好意思
l'm so, so sorry.
我向爸妈争取没人时 把她给关笼子里
l'm trying to talk my folks into caging her when there's company.
她太可爱了
She's so cute.
那...
Oh. So, um...
关于昨天的比赛 维吉尔
About the game yesterday, Virg.
对德里克来说非常重要
That was a really big deal for Derek.
他感到让整所学校都失望了
He feels like he let everybody in school down.
我本该赢了那场比赛
l would've won that game.
贾斯特突然裸奔球场
Chester streaked across the field
分散了他注意力    那些笨猪都中了什么邪?
and distracted him.
What's gotten into all the dorks?
都忘了自己的阵型
lt's like they just don't know their place anymore.
你们想让一分钟人
So you guys want the Minutemen
来阻止贾斯特干扰球赛?
to stop Chester from interfering with the game?
不是 我们想让你们做
Uh, no, man. We want you guys to do it.
谁是... 一分钟人?
Who are the... Minutemen?
我们
That's us.
没关系
Never mind.
我不知道
So, uh...    l don't know.
查理很难搞定    拜托了 维吉尔
Charlie's gonna be a tough sell.    Come on, Virg.
我知道我们不会再说
l know we never really talked about
高一那年的事儿了
what went down that day, freshman year.
事实是 我尽力去阻止他们了 但却没用
But the thing is, l tried to stop them. lt was a raw deal, man.
我希望你和我能回到过去
l wish you and l could get back to how we used to be.
哥们关系
Always chillin'.
你怎么想? 兄弟
What do you say, man?
帅呆了!
Scorch!
真不敢相信 德里克 这么对你 你还帮他?
l can't believe you want to help Derek after what he did to you?
这么对我们?    可能跟我们想的不一样
Did to us?    lt didn't happen the way we think.
何况 都过了很长时间了
And besides, it's time to move on.
我已经做了一些测试
l've been running some tests.
我们的时光穿梭已经损害了
We might be damaging the space-time
空间时间的连续性
continuum with our time travel.
这对我们的未来
That could have serious consequences
甚至整个星球都会有严重影响
to our future or even the planet.
德里克的比赛会这样都是我们的错
What happened to Derek in that game was our fault.
间接    他说的对 笑翠鸟
lndirectly.    He's right, Kookaburra.
在你从衣橱里就了他之后
Chester's a different person
贾斯特就变成了另外一个人
after you rescued him in the locker.
说到重点    是我做的吗?
Excellent point.    ls it me,
还是我让这个计划失去控制?
or have l totally lost control of this project?
失去控制 兄弟
Lost control, bro.
对不起 我迟了
Sorry l'm late.
放射网络
Activating grid.
是啊 我们不能忘带这勾子
Ah, yes. We mustn't forget the grappling hook.
每个人都要嘲笑我这个勾子 你们会后悔的
Everybody's gotta make fun of the hook. You'll all be sorry.
我永远也不会腻味这个
l will never get tired of that.
伙计们 你们看见了吗?
Hey, guys. You seen this?
"公羊队在最后时分击败黄蜂队"
来帮帮我 兄弟们?
Can l get a little help, guys?
伙计们 帮个小忙?
Guys, a little help?
保加 失球了 输了比赛
Beaugard loses the ball, fumbles the play.
哈密尔顿拿到球! 大黄蜂赢了!
Hamilton's got it! And the Hornets win.
因为你回来的时候
So because you took this tape with you
带上了这盒录像
when you jumped back in time...
它依然存在
lt still exists.
很聪明 对吧?    太疯狂了 伙计
Pretty clever, huh?    This is crazy, man.
你才是英雄!我要告诉其它人这件事
You're the man! l gotta tell the guys about this.
不行!    你不能那么做!
No!    You can't do that!
没必要! 这个是我们之间的秘密
This is too big. This has got to stay between us.
不用担心 兄弟 我们得庆祝庆祝
Yeah, yeah, no worries, brother. But we gotta celebrate.
明天会在我家狂欢 你也来吧
Tomorrow we're partying at my house and you gotta be there.
我想去 但不行 我和查理有约
Oh, l want to. l, l can't, though. l'm hanging out with Charlie.
天气网络系统
The Weather Network is counting down
全天候倒计时十大冰雹
the top ten hailstorms of all time.
我说出来才发现
l didn't realize how lame an evening
这晚上过的也太无聊了
that was till l said it out loud.
谢谢
Oh! Thank you.
Thanks.
开心吗?
So, you having fun?
是啊 我从十岁以来再没有参加过聚会
Oh, yeah. l haven't been to a party since l was ten.
记得一个扎马尾辫的女孩吐了我一身
And l remember the pony threw up on me.
那是我的生日聚会
That was my birthday party.        Oh.
开玩笑
l'm kidding.
那就好
Oh, good.
星期六会去舞会吧?
So l guess you're going to the dance Saturday?
应该会吧
Yeah, l guess.
听起来不太高兴
You don't sound happy about it.
我也不知道 德里克和我会参加每一个聚会
l don't know. Derek and l go to every party,
每一个社交场合
every social gathering.
想到都会恶心
lt's really a sickness when you think about it.
不知道
l don't know.
倍受欢迎看上去是一种很满足的生活方式
Being popular seems like a very satisfying way of life.
我也不太清楚
l don't know about that.
有时候在想 有没有选对路
Sometimes l wonder if l chose the right path.
看看你 看上去根本不在意...
l mean, look at you. You don't seem to mind that you're...
蠢猪的首领?
Captain of the dorks?
我没想要这么说
l wasn't going to say it like that.
老实说 你们看上去
But seriously, you guys look like
比其他人快乐
you're having so much more fun than everyone.
真的吗? 我们看来
Really? 'Cause from our side,
你们总是很开心的
it looks like you are having all the fun.
是吗?    当然
Really?    Yeah.
你好 维吉尔!    你好
Hey, Virg!    Hey.
真高兴又跟你一起聚会
lt is so good partying with you again.
替我谢谢那些兄弟 那个壮实的大家伙
Thank those other guys for me, the big, scary dude,
还有小笨蛋
and the little twerp.
噢 天 忘跟查理取消会面了
Oh! Dang it. l forgot to cancel with Charlie.
待会 我来跟他打个电话
Hold on, let me call him.
斯蒂芬妮过来看看    他应该都忘了
Stephanie, come see this.    He probably forgot all about it.
查理还要我道歉多少次?
Charlie, how many more times do l have to apologize?
还要212次
Two hundred and twelve times ought to do it.
查理听着 我非常非常抱歉!
Charlie, listen, l'm really, really sorry!
好吧... 原谅你
Fine... l forgive you.
我真的很累
Look, I'm just really frazzled.
我很担心时光机 还有骨牌效应
l'm worried about the time machine and possible ripple effects.
别挂 又来了个电话 我会打发掉的
Hang on, l've got another call. l'll get rid of them.
你好?
Hello?
维吉尔?
Hey, Virgil?
我不敢相信...    怎么了?
l can't believe l just...    What's wrong?
他...
He, um...
他...      哪也别去 我这就来
He, um...        Don't go anywhere. l'll be there.
斯蒂芬 斯蒂芬
Steph. Steph.
斯蒂芬妮?
Stephanie?
8年级的时候我就没再这样了
l haven't done this since eighth grade.
之前这里没有这个
That, that wasn't there before.
你应该走前门的
You could have used the front door.
是啊 但那有什么意思?
Yeah, but what fun would that be?
告诉我 发生什么了?
So tell me, what happened?
德里克很早就出去练习
So, Derek got out of practice early.
但我走出他家时 看见他在吻乔斯林·李
And when l went over to his house, l saw him kissing Jocelyn Lee.
斯蒂芬
Oh, Steph.
我早就知道
l knew it, too.
只是我不愿意相信
l just didn't want to believe it.
真是太蠢了
l feel so stupid.
我知道你很喜欢吃开心果
l know how much you like pistachio nuts, but
跑来时
in the rush to get here
我顺手买了一包
l accidentally grabbed a bag of pasta shells.
有意大利番茄酱吗?
Do you have any marinara sauce?
没有 我可以去买 如果...
No, l can go get some if you...
你在开玩笑
You're joking.
你能过来真的很好 维吉尔
lt was really nice of you to come over, Virg.
你真的是个很好的朋友
You're an amazing friend.
是啊...朋友
Yeah... friend.
喂?    宝贝儿 我们能把这事儿讲清楚吧?
Hello?    Babe, can we talk this out?
是德里克
lt's Derek.
听着 我和他谈谈
Listen, l'm going to talk to him.
我要一次性跟他结束了
l have to end it once and for all.
祝你好运
Good luck.
我没事儿!
l'm OK!
在初期发生后
These repeated irregularities are maintaining half-lives
这些不断重复的不规则反应仍然是半衰期
after their primary incidence.
真的非常奇怪
lt's totally weirdsville.
这很严重 先生
l mean, it's serious, sir. Um...
这波动直接从
The fluctuations are emanating directly
萨莫顿高中放射出来
from Summerton High School.
我对此有个理论
l actually have a theory about that.
它是...
lt's, well...
部门有与FBl联系过吗?
Does the department have any contacts at the FBl?
你有点可怕 有点不可接近
You know, you're kind of scary and unapproachable.
能和你坐一起吗?
Can we sit with you?
你根本清楚我的状况
You don't know what it's like to be me.
有名的运动员 非常受欢迎
Great athlete, hugely popular.
人们都希望我出现在赛场上
l mean, it's like people expect me to play the field.
还背叛了女朋友    你要说什么?
Cheat almost. What's your point?
但我没有 乔斯林主动的
But l didn't cheat. Jocelyn made the first move.
她吻了我 但我没有回吻她
She kissed me but l didn't kiss her back.
这不能算是背叛
That does not count as cheating.
这就是你要帮忙的
The thing is, and this is where you come in,
我希望你能及时的回到过去
l want you to go back in time
阻止斯蒂芬妮因为乔斯林跟我分手
and stop Stephanie from busting me with Jocelyn.
什么?
What?
我为什么要做?    因为我犯了大错
Why should l?    Because l made a big mistake.
非常大的错 我发誓再也不会发生了
A huge one. And it'll never happen again, l swear.
我不知道 你真的伤害了她
l don't know. l mean, you really hurt her.
我知道 我知道 我感觉很愧疚
l know. l know and l feel awful.
但是斯蒂芬和我已经在一起很长时间
But Steph and l have been going out a long time now.
每个男生都想得到她
She's everything a guy could ever want.
希望有天我们三个能再一起出去
l like that the three of us have been hanging out again.
像原来一样 它还是会像以前
Like the old days, and it could still be like that, man.
拜托 伙计 你怎么想?
Come on, buddy. What do you say?
我得考虑考虑    好的
l need to think about it.    Yeah.
当然
Yeah, sure.
怎么了? 抢劫
Hey! What's going on? Hold up.
系上安全带
Put on your seat belt.
我告诉你们 你们抓错人了
l'm tellin' you, you got the wrong guy.
但我可以告诉你们其他两个人的名字...
But l can give you the names of the two...
我正要告诉他们假名字 我是不会出卖你们的
l was gonna give them fake names. l'd never rat you out.
是啊
Yeah, right.
让我等一晚上电话的先生
Mr. ''Keep Me On Hold All Night.''
下午好 先生们
Good afternoon, gentlemen.
我是美国联邦调查局的
My name is Agent Rehnquist
瑞恩奎斯特特工
of the Federal Bureau of lnvestigation.
我要告诉你们一个秘密
And l'm going to let you boys in on a secret.
一个国家机密
A national secret.
1969年 在阿波罗号登月不久后
ln 1 969, shortly after the Apollo 1 1 moon landing,
美国政府开始建立
the United States government began funding
很多项科学计划
a number of new scientific projects.
其中一项就是时光穿梭
One of these projects was time travel.
什么?    时光穿梭?
What?    Time travel?
那就另当别论了    太科幻了
That's something else.    So science fiction-y.
拍好莱坞电影啊 这个...
Hollywood baloney. That's...
这个计划有了点结果
The project turned up little results
但最终还是停止了
and was eventually shut down.
文件再也没有被碰过
The files never again touched.
直到两个月前
That is until two months ago
一个费尽心机的人或群体
when an industrious individual, or individuals,
闯入NASA主机
broke into the NASA mainframe,
据我们追踪 用的是萨莫顿高中的电脑
using a computer which we traced to Summerton High School.
好吧! 我...
All right! l...
我朋友想说
What my friend was about to say is that
要是你不对我们进行任何控告
if you're not going to charge us with anything,
不能把我们拘留在这里 对吧 查查看
you can't keep us here. That's right, look it up.
我学过一学期政府
l took a semester of Government.
还得了个B-
Got a B minus.
我不明白 长官 为什么让他们离开?
l don't understand, sir. You're just letting them go?
监视能得到更多的信息
We can get more information by watching.
是啊 但现在他们知道我们在监视
Yeah, but now they know we're watching them.
是的 长官 真是绝妙的方案
Yes sir, excellent plan.
糟糕 太糟糕了
This is bad. Real bad.
是啊 恭喜啊 淘气的纳德
Yeah, way to go Naughty Ned.
因为你才会有FBI跟在我们后面
Thanks to you we have the FBl on our backs.
我?我几个星期前就想停下来了
Me? l wanted to stop this whole thing weeks ago!
但没有 你用它来谋取私利
But no, you had to use it for your own personal gain.
查理说的对 参加派对 与风云人物聚会
Charlie's right. Going to parties, hanging with the populars.
如果我没记错 你也得到不少好处
lf l remember correctly, you benefited too.
怎么了?    我们给了你生活
How so?    We gave you a life.
之前 你是人人都怕的大块头
Before us, you were this big guy everyone was afraid of.
你最好闭嘴 维吉尔    瞧
You better shut up, Virgil.    See.
你变自私了 维吉尔
You're being mean.
查理你怎么不回家
Charlie, why don't you just go home
看着你的电脑和猫?
to your computer and your cat.
我这就去
l will.
祝你在风光的新生活中好运
Good luck on your new life as a popular person.
我也走了
l'm outta here, too.
我过的很好 一直都很好
l'm better off on my own, l always have been.
这是最后的数据
Well, that's the last of the data.
很不幸 我们得到早上才会有答案
Unfortunately, we won't have an answer until morning.
对不起 没有一台超级电脑
Well, excuse me for not having a supercomputer.
你好?
Hello?
好 德里克
Oh. Hey, Derek.
怎么样? 维吉尔 要帮我吗? 伙计
What do you say, Virg? Gonna help me out, buddy?
当然...
Yeah, sure...
...D石头
...D-rock.
早 喜鹊!
Ahh!         Good morning, Magpie!
你妈妈让我进来的 今天真是不错的一天
Your mom let me in. lt is such a nice day l was thinking
也许 可以出去走走 谈谈我们的未来
we could go on a walk and talk about our future.
然后...
And then... oh!
我想要个橙子屋    结果!
l'd like an orange house.    The results!
你不需要地址 在信封上只用写
You wouldn't need an address. On the envelope you just say
"珍妮特·帕切拉斯科,橙子屋"
''Jeanette Pachelewski, orange house.''
完成了!
lt's done!
我不是个科学家
Oh, um, l'm no scientist,
但看上去情况不太妙
but that doesn't look good.
我们制造出了一个...一个...
We created a... a...
一个...一个...快说呀 蓝鸟
A... a... Spit it out, Bluebird.
一个黑洞
A black hole.
很糟糕 是不是?
That's bad, right?
随着时间的流失
As the timeline continues,
我们可以看到
we see an increased number of occurrences
在萨莫顿区域事件的扩大
here in the Summerton area.
如果我们都翻到47页 能看到加亮区...
lf we can all turn to page 47, we can see where l highlighted...
我撒谎了...
Hey!    l lied!
我偷了方程式
l stole the formula
我们进行了时间穿梭
we've been time-traveling all over the place.
先你一步 向你介绍太平洋技术中心地震部
Way ahead of you. l'd like you to meet Doctors Connors
康纳斯博士和温多普博士
and Winthorpe from the seismology department at Pacific Tech.
博士 这是查理·塔特尔
Doctors, this is Charles Tuttle.
你是谁? 9岁男孩    他14岁
What are you, nine years old?    He's fourteen.
好些了 现在不觉得是个失败者了
That's better. Now l don't feel like such a loser.
那你们已经知道黑洞的事了?
So you already know about the black hole?
什么?    黑洞!
What?    The black hole!
我知道你们资金不足 但别这样
l knew you guys were underfunded, but come on.
真可笑 我们想过各种最坏的结果
Preposterous. We ran the worst case scenario several times.
从没想到过黑洞
We never came up with a black hole.
我发现有五六个小数没有继续
l see five, six decimals that weren't carried over.
噢
Hmm.
是啊 "噢"
Oops.    Yeah, oops.
每次我们用那个机器
Each time we used the machine
空间时间连续性上的裂缝
the rift in the space-time continuum
就没有消失 现在这些波动合在了一起
did not disappear. lnstead the fluctuations blended together
形成了一个巨大的黑洞
to create one giant black hole.
黑洞最严重的地区会扩展开
The worst part is the black hole
直到吞掉"萨莫顿"
will spread until it swallows up Summerton.
然后就是整个西北 接着是整个美国
Then the Northwest, then the entire United States.
以此类推
And so on.
还剩多久?
How much time till zero hour?
据我估计...
According to my estimates we have...
...离世界毁灭还剩不到4小时
...less than four hours till the end of the world.
伙计们 我们要拉响红色警报
OK, people, we are going to Code Red.
接通华盛顿 马上
Get Washington on the phone, now!
有一个方法可以扭转局势 不过是个远射
There might be a way to reverse it, but it's a longshot.
说来听听吧 长官
Well, let's hear it, sir.
今晚的舞会让我激动 维吉尔
l'm excited for the dance tonight.
你知道吗?
And you know what?
我真高兴你能跟我来
l'm really glad you're coming with me.
要不朋友是干什么的?    少来
Hey, what are friends for?    Come on.
一切就绪?    是的
Everything set?    Uh, yeah.
衣服在棒球场
The suits are in the basement
我们穿过咖啡厅下的隧道过去
we'll go through the tunnels under the cafeteria.
挺好 他们一宣布赢家我们就走
Sweet. We'll go as soon as they announce the winners.
好啊 维吉尔
Hey, Virgil.
斯蒂芬...
Steph...
你相信人的一生
Do you believe that a person's life
在一瞬间就能改变吗?
can change in a single moment?
有时是变好 有时只会更烂?
Sometimes for the better, other times for the worse?
我想是的
Yeah, l guess.
我们生命中的一刻即将被改写
There's a moment in one of our lives that's about to change.
不知道是会变好还是变坏
And l don't know if it's for the better or for the worse.
维吉尔 我不大明白
Virgil, um, l'm not following.
注意...
Uh, attention...
大家都注意了
Um, attention everyone.
该是宣布舞会国王和王后的时候了
lt's time to announce this year's king and queen of the dance.
但先来段...
But first...
宝贝 雷德 我想热一点
Sonny, Red, and l wanna fry up some
花生黄油和香蕉三明治
peanut butter and banana sandwiches.
谢谢 非常感谢
Thank you. Thank you very much.
这是猫王艾维斯·普里斯莱 有人知道吗?
lt's Elvis Presley. Anyone?
不会吧 是个很有天赋的...随便吧
Come on, that was a brilliant... Whatever.
斯蒂芬妮·詹姆森还有维吉尔·福克斯
Stephanie Jameson and Virgil Fox
上来吧 你们赢了
get up here. You won.
真让人吃惊    哪有
This is such a surprise.    Not really.
为了保证我们能赢
To guarantee we'd win
我准时赶回来 塞满了投票箱
l went back in time and stuffed the ballot box.
什么?
What?
詹姆森小姐和福克斯先生
Miss Jameson and Mr. Fox.
别让它离开你脑袋 还有时间查票
Don't let it go to your head. There's still time for a recount.
你真的塞满了那个盒子?
So, um, did you really stuff the box?
是的
Yeah.
你 当然 不然谁会投我票?
l mean, you, sure, but who would vote for me?
我会
l would.
这太奇怪了    是啊
This is weird.    Yeah.
为什么?    一个不错的奇怪
Why?    A good weird.
确实    你怎么能跟某人做这么长
Right.    How you can be friends with someone
时间的朋友...
for so long, then...
这不一样    一个不错的不一样
lt's different..    A good different.
来吧 兄弟 该走了    噢 关于那个
Come on, brother, it's time to go.    Oh, about that.
我想 我反悔了    你答应过的
l think l changed my mind.    You promised.
维吉尔?    哪也别去 我待会就回来
Virgil?    Don't go anywhere. l'll be right back.
我知道维吉尔抢走斯蒂芬妮会让德雷克抓狂
l knew Derek would be hacked about Virgil bringing Stephanie.
打!
Fight!
不    打 打
Oh, no.    Fight, fight.
德里克 等等 我们能谈谈吗?
Derek, wait up. Can we talk about this?
哦 天哪
Oh, man.
斯蒂芬妮 维吉尔去哪儿了?
Stephanie, where's Virgil?
他和德里克出去了    为什么?
He left with Derek.    Why?
别告诉我他又要跳回到过去?
Don't tell me he's going to jump back in time?
上帝 他就是要这么做!
Oh my gosh, that's what he's doing!
他会把事情搞的一团糟的!
He might make things worse!
借过! 对不起!    比世界末日还要糟糕?
Excuse me! Sorry!    Worse than the end of the world?
德里克 我不能这么做
Derek, l don't think l can do this.
什么? 为什么?
What, why?
斯蒂芬妮 我只是...只是觉得...
Stephanie. l just... l just think...
伙计 别告诉我 你想要抢我的女人
Dude, don't tell me you're going to try to steal my girl.
你是我的朋友 朋友之间不能那么做
We're friends. l mean, buddies don't do that to each other.
维吉尔! 维吉尔·福克斯!
Virgil! Virgil Fox!
维吉尔 我们有点小麻烦
Virgil, we have a small problem.
只剩不到一个小时来拯救整个星球!
We have less than an hour to save the planet!
你在说什么?
What are you talking about?
好吧 好吧 这里怎么了?
Well, well. What do we have here, hmm?
看来要开始一场骚乱
Looks like the beginnings of a fracas.
一场什么?    一场骚乱!
A what?    A fracas!
战争    晚上留校
lt's a fight.    We'll sort out the detentions later.
现在 大家都回到体育馆
Right now, all of you get back to the gym.
都动起来!
Everyone move!
都不许动! FBl!
Everyone freeze! FBl!
不许动! ClA!
Stop! ClA!
计量局!
Bureau of Weights and Measures!
以后 你得先出来
ln the future, you should probably go first.
维吉尔 这正是我要说的 来吧
Virgil, that's what l was talking about. Come on.
我们得赶快把所有人撤离!
We need to get these people out of here now!
那我们得进黑洞 关闭它?
So, we're supposed to go inside the black hole and close it?
据我所知 这是唯一的出路
As far as l can figure, it's the only way.
我们要带着这个控制器
We'll take the remote pack with us
改变我们着陆的极性
and reverse the polarity once we land.
什么东西?    我一直在研究
What pack?    l've been working on
一种控制我们从另一边跳出的新方法
a new way to control our jumps from the other side.
好吧 带上电话
OK, hold the phone.
我们不能让学生进去 他们会死的
We can't let these students go in that, they could die!
别无选择
We have no choice.
他们是唯一熟悉使用这个仪器的人
They're the only ones familiar with the equipment.
要是他们不去 我们就得死
lf they don't go then we could all die.
快点
God speed.
是我把一切弄的一团糟
l'm the one who messed everything up.
我进去 查理和齐克跟这个没关系
l'll go. Charlie and Zeke had nothing to do with it.
什么叫没关系? 是我发明的
What do you mean, nothing to do with it? l invented it.
我是帮凶    不 你没有
l helped.    No, you didn't.
我有过    你刷的油漆!
Yeah, l did.    You painted it!
打扰一下
Excuse me.
好吧 够了 够了
OK. Enough! Enough!
你们都去
You'll both go.
你们也需要我 长官 还有我的钩子
You'll be needing me too, sir, and my hook.
听着 我们一旦转换了黑洞的极性
Listen, guys, once we've reversed the wormhole's polarity,
无法计算 多长时间后会关闭
there's no measuring how quickly it will close.
它可能会开几分钟
lt could stay open for several more minutes
也有可能会瞬间消失
or vanish instantaneously.
要是我们活着完成任务
And even if we do make it back alive,
不能保证
there's no guarantee
我们能回到此刻
we'll return exactly to the point we exited from.
好的 好的    好运 齐克!
Aye aye, Ser Positive.    Good luck, Zeke!
维吉尔 听说你要去拯救世界
Virgil, l hear you're trying to save the world.
对啊 你哥哥很酷吧?
That's right. Your big brother's pretty cool, huh?
要是你死了 我可以用你的房间吗? 我的太小了...
When you die can l have your room? Mine is way too small and...
拜 艾米    查理
Bye, Amy.    Charlie, um...
安全回来 好吗?
Come back in one piece, OK?
快点 查理 我们要走了 查理
Come on, Charlie, we gotta go. Charlie?
查理?
Charlie?
醒醒    没事儿 齐克
Here.    All right, Zeke.
维吉尔
Virgil.
你可以的
You can do it!
听着 我...不管发生什么 我只想让你知道...
Listen, l just... whatever happens, l just want you to know...
伙计 好运 一切顺利
Hey man, good luck. With everything.
是啊 太好了
Yeah, great.
要...
Just, um...
万事小心
Just be careful.
行吗?    好的
OK?    OK.
一分钟人 一分钟人 一分钟人
Minutemen! Minutemen! Minutemen!
至少最后他们正了名
At least they finally got the name right.
一起吧 伙伴们!
Let's do this, fellas!
太酷了
Whoa. Cool.
太空人
Wow! Space men!
我们到绿野仙踪了
l think we landed in Munchkinland.
酷毙了 怎么了 小鬼?
Cool. What up, Munchkins?
我们穿过了小镇 来到公园了
Actually, we're across town at the park.
你们来自那个星球? 海王星?
What planet did you come from? From Neptune?
海王星上的人吃通心粉吗? 我喜欢通心粉
Do people on Neptune eat macaroni? l love macaroni.
通心粉是蔬菜吗?
ls macaroni a vegetable?
打住 小鬼 我们要在这儿工作
Beat it, kid. We're workin' here.
架好天线
OK, set up the antenna.
开始转换序列
Beginning reversal sequence.
来吧
Come on.
太帅了
Wow! Sweet!
看上去不错
This looks good!
扩张速度放慢了!
Rate of increase is slowing!
漩涡的极性在减弱
The vortex's polarity is decreasing.
平稳了!
Stabilization achieved!
成功了!    哈!
l think we did it!    Ha!
漩涡接触到地面还有20分钟
We have 20 minutes till the vortex touches the ground.
然后我们就能回去了
Then we can jump back.
嘿 伙计们
Hey, guys.
今天是2005年9月3号
Today is September 3rd, 2005.
高中第一天
First day of school freshman year.
就是这天...    "那个事件"
Oh, that's the day...    ''The lncident.''
"那个事件"    是啊
''The lncident.''    Of course!
量子加速器模块
The day a module of quantum acceleration
第一次涉及空间时间连续性!火箭车
first interacted with the space-time continuum! The rocket cart.
它联系着我们
lt's linked the wormhole from
现在到过去的这个时候
our present to this moment in the past.
不久后 我们...    兄弟
ln a few moments our...    Dude.
不要这样 维吉尔
Don't do it, Virgil.
维吉尔 不要!
Virg, no!
维吉尔 慢点!
Virg, come on!
你想阻止即将发生的一切?
You're thinking of stopping what's going on there?
为什么不? 这不正是一分钟人要做的吗?
Why not? lsn't that what the Minutemen do?
要阻止的错误吗
Un-do mistakes?
我在那儿做错了一件事
Well, l made a mistake down there.
我有机会成为大人物
l have a chance to be somebody.
好吧 但你得知道
OK, but know this.
下面所发生的 是我们成了好朋友
What happened down there is we became friends.
那天我们一起绑在蠢公羊雕像上
That day that we were tied up together on that stupid Ram statue.
这天
This day.
你恨的这天 只是因为让你有点尴尬
This day you hate so much because you got a little embarrassed?
但是我最爱的一天
This is my favorite day.
虽然我还是个讨厌鬼 但这又有什么
Even though l'd still be a nerd, it didn't really matter anymore,
因为我有了真正的朋友
because now l had a real friend.
这会让一切都好起来
And that would always make everything OK.
这就够了
So much for always, l guess.
听着 听着 维吉尔
Listen... listen, Virg,
你想做什么就做什么
you do what you gotta do here.
要是事物的另一面不一样
And if things aren't the same on the other side...
也是种不错的选择
...it's been a good ride.
伙计们 等等 你们不应该这么做
Hey guys, wait! You shouldn't do that.
因为我有个更好的主意
'Cause l've got a much better idea.
为什么不把这个涂他们身上?
l mean, why don't we smear this all over them?
失败者
Losers.
不 不 漩涡关闭时间快耗尽!
No! No! The closure rate of the vortex went into overdrive!
你是说...    漩涡马上就要碰到地面了
You're telling me...    lf that touches the ground,
我们会永远被困在这里的
we'll be trapped here for good.
那维吉尔怎么办?    我们不可能去找他
What about Virgil?    There's no way we'll make it to him
并且准时到达漩涡!
and back to the vortex in time!
查理! 查理 起来!
Charlie! Charlie, get up!
起来 查理! 我们得快跑
Get up, Charlie! We gotta keep moving!
走吧!
Let's go!
赶不上了
We're never going to make it.
还有1英里远 我们永远被困在过去了
We're a mile away. We're stuck in the past forever.
兄弟们 你们不想回去了
Man, you do not want to go back there.
橄榄球员把学生粗鲁的挂起来 这是太龌龊了
Kids getting roughed up by football players. lt's real ugly.
你说什么?
You don't say?
开始 是有点为小破孩感到抱歉 但
At first, l felt kinda sorry for the dorky kid, but...
我意识到 他还为我做什么?
...then l realized, what does he need me for?
他有一个好朋友在那里
He's got himself a great friend down there.
总有一天 他还会有其他的好朋友
And someday he'll have other great friends, too.
帅呆了!
Scorch!
我们握手言和吧
You know, let's come up with our own handshake.
我们可以走了吗?
Can we go?
我不想再重复三年高中
l don't feel like repeating three years of high school.
对啊 抱歉    好主意 冲 冲啊
Right. Sorry.    Good idea! Go, go!
系上安全带!
Seatbelts!
小心!
Look out!
车!
Car!    Ahh!
天哪!
Oh my God!    Whoa, whoa!
干什么啊?!    什么意思啊?
What are you doing?!    What do you mean?
那是第十四大街 漩涡在后面
That was 1 4th Street! The vortex is back that way.
我的错
Oh, my bad.
我们赶不上了!    没问题
We're never gonna make it!    No problem.
铁钩!
Whoa!         Yeah, grappling hook!
击个掌!
Oh my God!          Yeah!
手抓住轮子!
Now keep your hand on the wheel!
冲啊 维吉尔!    快冲啊 不然赶不上了!
Go, Virgil!    Go or we're not gonna make it!
我们快赶不上了!
We're not gonna make it!
一分钟人准则!
Minutemen rule!
我的火箭车呢?
Where's my rocket cart?
这是哪天?
What day is it?
够了 不要再时间穿梭了!
That is it. No more time travel!
听着 你们应该在慢跑
OK, up. You're supposed to be jogging.
我的体育课不准任何人偷懒
Now, nobody loafs in my gym class.
你不了解!    我了解的够多了!
You don't understand!    l understand plenty!
我知道你没有慢跑 动起来 走吧
l understand you're not jogging. So let's move it! Let's go!
走 走 走
Go! Go! Go!
开始慢跑 快动 快动 快动
Start jogging! Move it, move it, move it!
我也要一件那么帅的慢跑服
l got to get one of those cool jogging suits.
冒烟的轮胎?
A smoking tire?
行了 同学们
All right, people
不准在走廊闲逛 走开
no loitering in the hallways. Let's move it along.
走开 快 快
Go!
我一定要给学校立定一个穿着制度
l'm definitely gonna institute a dress code in this place!
瞧 斯蒂芬 我需要她的帮助
See, Steph, l need her help.
我根本听不懂你在讲什么
l have no idea what you just said.
我说"我的男朋友是一个说谎的弱智"
l said, ''My boyfriend is a lying cheesebrain.''
别这样 斯蒂芬    德里克我要学习
Come on, Steph.    Derek, l'm trying to study.
你们知道吗?这天我们第一次时光穿梭
You know what? This is the first day we time traveled.
这一天我们想中彩票
The day we tried to win the lottery.
衣服真不赖 大块头
Wow, nice outfits, bozos.
好啊 德里克
Hey, Derek.
与乔斯林过的开心
Have fun with Jocelyn.
什么意思?
What's that supposed to mean?
我不知道 你们俩嘴上功夫真不赖
Oh, l don't know. l figured you're both so good with lipstick,
你们真是天造地设的一对
you'd make a perfect match.
你总是像一头蠢猪一样 维吉尔
You were always gonna be a dork anyway, Virgil.
你一直就是笨蛋 德里克
And you were always gonna be a jerk, Derek.
祝你生活愉快
Have a nice life.
女士们    噢 新衣服呀 美冠鹦鹉?
Ladies.    Oh, what's new, Cockatoo?
你看上去像个超级英雄    谢谢 小南瓜
Wow, you look like a superhero.    Thanks, pumpkin.
你还没有吻过她
You've never kissed her.
那个在走廊上的事儿还没发生呢
The scene in the hallway hasn't happened yet.
噢 是啊 珍妮特不好意思
Oh, right. Jeanette, l'm sorry!
刚才只是... 我有原因的
l was just... l can explain.
嘿 没事儿
Hey, it's OK.
好 斯蒂芬    噢 好
Uh, Steph.    Oh, hey.
你刚才没在这儿看见我 是吧?
You didn't see me in here before, did you?
没有 怎么穿这么奇怪的外套?
No, and um... what's with the weird suit?
刚才我彩排了学校一个
Oh, l was just rehearsing a little school play
关于时光穿梭的剧 让我想了很多
about time travel and, uh, it kinda got me thinking.
要是真能回到过去 我会改变什么
lf l really could go back in time, what would l change?
这件雪衣?
That snowsuit?
我会告诉斯蒂芬妮对她的感觉
l would tell Stephanie how l really feel about her.
我觉得她很棒
That l think she's great.
真的?    是的
Really?    Yeah.
要是我能回到过去
And if l could go back in time...
我也会告诉维吉尔同样的话
...l think l'd tell Virgil the same thing.
维吉尔!    什么?
Virgil!    What?
查理!
Charlie!
"远距传物"对你来说有什么意义吗?
What does the word ''teleportation'' mean to you?
比时光穿梭还要强
lt's bigger than time travel
一种新的运输典范
a whole new transportation paradigm.
我们依然需要幻灯机...
We still have the slide projector...
我会打电话给你的
l'll call you.
听上去想时间穿梭    不要 查理
lt's like time travel.    No, Charlie.
黑洞!    跟着我
Black hole!    Follow me.
斯蒂芬妮 听我说!
Stephanie, listen to me!
告诉他 他喜欢你 你会喜欢他的
Talk to him, he likes you! You'll like him!
想想油价 想想全球变暖
Think about gas prices. Think about global warming.
我会让珍妮特回来的!
l could get Jeanette back!
"两周后"
好 我们来了 什么急事?
OK, we're here. Where's the fire?
先生们 做好心理准备
Ah, gentlemen, brace yourselves,
这在整个人类历史
for this is going to be the greatest invention...
将会是一项伟大的发明
ln the history of all mankind.
虾仁馅饼不是个好主意
Whoa. l knew the shrimp tacos were a bad idea.
你又做一个...他又做了一个查理
You made another... He made another Charlie.
是的 我发现了
Yeah. l got that.
多伟大啊?
How great is this?
我不觉得"伟大"是个合适的词    "恐怖"怎么样?
l'm not sure ''great'' is the word.    ''Terrible''?
就是这个    想想可能性
Yeah. That's it.    Think of the possibilities.
现实实用性? 你有小提琴课
The practical applications? You have a violin lesson,
但你还想看企业联合组织审判节目
but you also want to catch Judge Judy.
没问题 这就解决方法
No problemo. Here's the solution.
或者你可以录下来
Or you could just record it.    Mmm.
这例子不好
Bad example.
我要同一学期上AP历史和AP物理
l'm taking AP history and AP physics the same semester,
但我的课又超量了
but for some reason l'm on academic overload,
最后没有时间复习考试...
and don't have time to study for both finals...
伙计们    你们要干什么?
Guys.    What are you doing?
齐克 维吉尔    这是我的胳膊
Zeke, Virgil.    That's my arm.
你们要去哪儿? 你们不能把我们留在里面
Where are you going? You can't leave us in here.
至少你有个伴
At least you'll have company.
咱们团队怎么样?一分钟人又开始了!
What about the team? Minutemen ride again!
我喜欢这个想法 来个团队怎样?
l like that. What about the team?
这孩子真的很爱科学
That kid really loves science.
是啊
Yeah.
挖苦结束 来个小脆饼吧
Hey, scooch over. l'm going for the pretzel nubs.
那我们就是要进黑洞 把它关起来?
So, we're supposed to go inside the black hole and close it?
据我所知 这是唯一的方法
As far as l can figure, it's the only way.